smashits.com 2012-09-15

# A1 Bollywood Hindi Tamil Telugu Indian Music Videos Songs Soundtracks Movie Film and News - SmasHits.com

Updated May 24, 2011 **OUR PRIVACY POLICY**

SmasHits.com recognizes that its customers, visitors, users, and others who use http://SmasHits.com value their privacy. This Privacy Notice details important information regarding the use and disclosure of User information collected on the SmasHits.com site. SmasHits.com provides this Privacy Notice to help you make an informed decision about whether to use or continue using the SmasHits.com Sites. 

This Privacy Notice is incorporated into and is subject to the SmasHits.com Terms of Use. Your use of the SmasHits.com Sites and any personal information you provide on the SmasHits.com Sites remains subject to the terms of this Privacy Notice and our Terms of Use. 

Please note that any video, image, or other content posted at the direction of Users onto the SmasHits.com Sites becomes published content and is not considered personally identifiable information subject to this Privacy Notice. 

**Information SmasHits.com Collects**

User Provided Information: You provide certain personally identifiable information (such as your name and email address) to SmasHits.com when choosing to participate in various activities on the SmasHits.com Sites such as uploading videos, posting messages in our forums or in the video comments section, entering contests or sweepstakes, taking advantage of promotions, responding to surveys, or subscribing to newsletters or other mailing lists. 

Personal Information: Use of certain features of the Service may require submission of certain personal information, including your first and last name, email address, a nick name (or other user ID) and a password. 

Non personally identifiable Information: SmasHits.com may also collect or receive additional non personally identifiable usage information specifically related to the use of a particular feature or offering on the SmasHits.com Service or website(s), and responses to the offerings and advertisements presented on SmasHits.com's Service and/or website(s). 

SmasHits.com may also collect or receive (in some cases as part of the internet communication protocol) certain non-personally identifiable technical information, when the SmasHits.com website(s) and pages are visited or when the SmasHits.com Service is used. 

Cookies Information: When you visit the SmasHits.com Sites, we may send one or more cookies - a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. SmasHits.com uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser. Your browser may use persistent cookies on subsequent visits to the site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser help file directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the SmasHits.com Sites may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled. 

Log File Information: When you use the SmasHits.com Sites, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser language, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, the date and time of your request, and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. 

**The Way SmasHits.com Uses Information**

The information is used to operate and improve the features, offerings and content presented to you by SmasHits.com, to personalize the content and advertisements provided to you ; to fulfill your requests for Services, programs, and services; to communicate with you and respond to your inquiries; to conduct research about your use of the Service and/or website(s), offerings and advertisements presented on SmasHits.com Service, email communication, website(s) and pages; and to help offer you other Services, programs, or services that may be of interest. If at some point Smashits sells all or a portion of its assets, customer information is one of those assets that would be transferred or acquired by a third party; the third party would then have the right to continue using the personal information as set forth in this policy. 

Any personally identifiable information of yours will not be shared with third parties unless you have consented to the sharing of this information. SmasHits.com may use this information to present offers to you on behalf of business partners and advertisers. These business partners and advertisers may receive aggregate data about various groups of SmasHits.com users, but do not receive information that personally identifies you. 

1\. Any personal information or video content that you voluntarily disclose online (on discussion boards, in messages and chat areas, within your public profile page, etc.) becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others. Your account name (not your email address) is displayed to other Users when you upload videos or send messages through the SmasHits.com Sites and other Users can contact you through messages and comments. Any videos that you submit to the SmasHits.com Sites may be redistributed through the Internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public. 

2\. We do not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. We may, however, use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major SmasHits.com Site changes or for customer service purposes). 

3\. We use both your personally identifiable information and certain non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous User usage data, cookies, IP addresses, browser type, clickstream data, etc.) to improve the quality and design of the SmasHits.com Sites and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, and analyzing User preferences and trends. 

**When SmasHits.com discloses Information**

SmasHits.com reserves the right to disclose personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information that SmasHits.com believes, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to enforce our Terms of Use, take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend itself against any third-party claims or allegations, to assist government enforcement agencies, to protect the security or integrity of our web site, and to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of SmasHits.com, our Users or others. 

**Changes and updates to this Privacy Notice**

This Privacy Notice may be revised periodically. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. In general, we only use your personal information in the manner described in the Privacy Notice in effect when we received the personal information you provided. Your continued use of the SmasHits.com Sites constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Notice and any future revisions. 

For revisions to this Privacy Notice that may be materially less restrictive on our use or disclosure of the personal information you have already provided to us, we will attempt to obtain your consent before implementing such revisions with respect to such information. 

**Third Parties' Practices**

This Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices exercised by other provides of products or services, advertisers or other web sites, or companies/people that SmasHits.com does not own or control, or does not employ or manage. 

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our website. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. to learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [networkadvertising.org](http://networkadvertising.org/).
